A Guide to the Bureau of Social Hygiene records FA060
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects, 3
  - Projects - Juvenile Delinquency, 3_3
    - Juvenile Courts, 1931-1934 (Box 13, Folder 235)
    - Juvenile Detention Homes, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 236)
    - Juvenile Detention Homes, 1930-1933 (Box 14, Folder 237)
    - Juvenile Detention Homes, 1930-1933 (Box 14, Folder 238)
    - Juvenile Detention Homes, 1930-1933 (Box 14, Folder 239)
    - Juvenile Detention Homes, 1930-1933 (Box 14, Folder 240)
    - Juvenile Detention Homes - Clippings and Pamphlets (Box 14, Folder 241)
    - New Jersey State Home for Boys, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 242)
    - New School for Social Research, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 243)
    - New York State Training School for Boys, 1932-1936 (Box 14, Folder 244)
    - "The Police and Boys' Work" by Leroy Peterson, 1927-1928 (Box 14, Folder 245)
    - Welfare Council, 1926-1934 (Box 14, Folder 246)
    - Welfare Council, 1926-1934 (Box 14, Folder 247)
    - Whittier School Project, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 248)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1925 (Box 14, Folder 249)
      New York survey.
    - Pamphlets (Box 14, Folder 250)
      Includes Children's Village (Dobbs Ferry, New York) and the New York Training School for Boys.
  - Projects - Criminology, 3_4
    This subseries has material on projects such as the Massachusetts State Prison Colony, Associates for Government Service, Uniform Criminal Statistics, Police Training Schools, and the Institute of Criminology at Columbia. It also contains information on publications like "European Policy Systems" and general information on criminology, prisons, and probation.
    - American Bar Association, 1928-1935 (Box 15, Folder 251)
    - American Law Institute, 1927-1935 (Box 15, Folder 252)
    - American Law Institute, 1927-1935 (Box 15, Folder 253)
    - "American Police Systems" by Raymond Fosdick, 1914-1930 (Box 15, Folder 254)
    - American Prison Association, 1928-1934 (Box 15, Folder 255)
    - Associates for Government Service, 1927-1932 (Box 15, Folder 256)
    - Associates for Government Service, 1927-1932 (Box 15, Folder 257)
    - Associates for Government Service - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 258)
    - Association of Grand Jurors, 1928-1933 (Box 15, Folder 259)
      New York County.
    - Association of Grand Jurors, 1928-1933 (Box 15, Folder 260)
    - Association of Grand Jurors, 1928-1933 (Box 15, Folder 261)
    - Association of Grand Jurors - Clippings and Pamphlets (Box 15, Folder 262)
    - Association of Grand Jurors - Clippings and Pamphlets (Box 15, Folder 263)
    - Barry, A. G., 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 264)
    - Bates, Sanford, 1928-1933 (Box 15, Folder 265)
    - Berkeley Behavioral Research Clinic, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 266)
    - Case Histories - Sample Forms, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 267)
    - Cockerell's Reading Course, 1929-1931 (Box 16, Folder 268)
    - Committee of 14, 1928-1933 (Box 16, Folder 269)
    - Conference on Penal Statistics, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 270)
    - Conference on Penal Statistics, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 271)
    - Crime Prevention Bureau, 1930-1932 (Box 16, Folder 272)
      New York City Police Department.
    - Crime Studies, 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 273)
    - Crime Statistics, 1927-April 1930 (Box 16, Folder 274)
    - Crime Statistics, 1927-April 1930 (Box 16, Folder 275)
    - Crime Statistics, 1927-April 1930 (Box 16, Folder 276)
    - Crime Statistics, May 1930-1933 (Box 17, Folder 277)
    - Crime Statistics, May 1930-1933 (Box 17, Folder 278)
    - Crime Statistics, May 1930-1933 (Box 17, Folder 279)
    - Crime Statistics, May 1930-1933 (Box 17, Folder 280)
    - Crime Statistics, May 1930-1933 (Box 17, Folder 281)
    - Crime Statistics, May 1930-1933 (Box 17, Folder 282)
    - Crime Statistics - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 283)
    - Criminal Justice, 1933-June 1934 (Box 17, Folder 284)
    - Criminal Justice, 1933-June 1934 (Box 17, Folder 285)
    - Criminal Justice, July 1934-1935 (Box 18, Folder 286)
    - Criminal Justice, July 1934-1935 (Box 18, Folder 287)
    - Criminology, 1914-1934 (Box 18, Folder 288)
    - Criminology, 1914-1934 (Box 18, Folder 289)
    - Criminology, 1914-1934 (Box 18, Folder 290)
    - Criminology, 1914-1934 (Box 18, Folder 291)
    - Criminology, 1914-1934 (Box 18, Folder 292)
    - Criminology, 1935-1936 (Box 19, Folder 293)
    - Criminal Legislation, 1914-1933 (Box 19, Folder 294)
    - Criminal Legislation, 1914-1933 (Box 19, Folder 295)
    - Criminological Research Bulletin, 1932-1936 (Box 19, Folder 296)
    - Criminological Research Project, 1934-1935 (Box 19, Folder 297)
    - "Criminology Survey" by Leonard Harrison, 1935-1936 (Box 19, Folder 298)
    - "Criminology Survey" by Leonard Harrison, 1935-1936 (Box 19, Folder 299)
    - "Criminology Survey" by Leonard Harrison - Reports (Box 19, Folder 300)
    - Commercial Crime Commission, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 301)
    - "Decline of the Prison Population of England" by E. H. Sutherland, 1929-1934 (Box 20, Folder 302)
    - "Decline of the Prison Population of England" by E. h. Sutherland - Reports (Box 20, Folder 303)
    - Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research, 1929-1931 (Box 20, Folder 304)
    - Eastern-Southern Conference on State Institutional Labor, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 305)
    - "European Police Systems" by Raymond Fosdick, 1912-1935 (Box 20, Folder 306)
    - "European Police Systems" by Raymond Fosdick, 1912-1935 (Box 20, Folder 307)
    - "European Police Systems" by Raymond Fosdick - Charts (Box 20, Folder 308)
    - "European Police Systems" by Raymond Fosdick - Acknowledgements (Box 20, Folder 309)
    - "European Police Systems" by Raymond Fosdick - Acknowledgements (Box 20, Folder 310)
    - "European Police Systems" by Raymond Fosdick - Acknowledgements (Box 20, Folder 311)
    - "European Police Systems" - Clippings (Box 21, Folder 312)
    - "European Police Systems" - Clippings (Box 21, Folder 313)
    - "European Police Systems" - Clippings (Box 21, Folder 314)
    - Fall River Project, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 315)
    - Federal Council of Churches, 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 316)
    - Fellowships - Maurice Blodgett, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 317)
    - Fellowships - John Dickey, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 318)
    - Fellowships - Howard Leahy, 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 319)
    - Fellowships - Rudolf Lehmann, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 320)
    - Fellowships - Alexander Paterson, 1929-1933 (Box 21, Folder 321)
    - Fellowships - Alexander Paterson, 1929-1933 (Box 21, Folder 322)
    - Fellowships - A. W. Stearns, 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 323)
    - Fellowships - Richard Winslow, 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 324)
    - Fingerprint Indexing, 1929-1935 (Box 21, Folder 325)
    - Folton, Edgar, 1928-1931 (Box 21, Folder 326)
    - Fordham University, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 327)
    - Gates, Merrill, 1929-1931 (Box 22, Folder 328)
    - Gaudet Project, 1930-1931 (Box 22, Folder 329)
    - Gill, Howard, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 330)
    - Harvard Crime Survey, 1926-1935 (Box 22, Folder 331)
    - Harvard Crime Survey, 1926-1935 (Box 22, Folder 332)
    - Harvard Crime Survey, 1926-1935 (Box 22, Folder 333)
    - Harvard Crime Survey, 1926-1935 (Box 22, Folder 334)
    - Harvard Crime Survey, 1926-1935 (Box 22, Folder 335)
    - Harvard Crime Survey - Draft, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 336)
    - Harvard Crime Survey - Draft, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 337)
    - Harvard Institute of Criminal Law, 1929-1932 (Box 22, Folder 338)
    - Harvard Institute of Criminal Law, 1929-1932 (Box 22, Folder 339)
    - Harvard Institute of Criminal Law, 1933-1935 (Box 23, Folder 340)
    - Identification Methods, French and English, 1926 (Box 23, Folder 341)
    - Individualization Conference, 1931 (Box 23, Folder 342)
    - Institute of Criminological Research, 1933-1934 (Box 23, Folder 343)
    - Institute of Criminology, 1929-1936 (Box 23, Folder 344)
    - Institute of Criminology, 1929-1936 (Box 23, Folder 345)
    - Institute of Criminology, 1929-1936 (Box 23, Folder 346)
    - Institute of Criminology, 1929-1936 (Box 23, Folder 347)
    - Institute of Criminology, 1929-1936 (Box 23, Folder 348)
    - Institute of Criminology, 1929-1936 (Box 23, Folder 349)
    - Institute of Criminology, 1929-1936 (Box 23, Folder 350)
    - Institute of Criminology, 1929-1936 (Box 23, Folder 351)
    - Institute of Criminology, 1929-1936 (Box 23, Folder 352)
    - Institute of Criminology - Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 353)
    - Institute of Criminology - Comments and Criticisms (Box 24, Folder 353A)
    - Institute of Criminology - Opinions (Box 24, Folder 353B)
    - Institute of Criminology - Opinions (Box 24, Folder 353C)
    - Institute of Criminology - Social Science Research Council Comments (Box 24, Folder 354)
    - Institute of Criminology - Harrison Critique (Box 25, Folder 355)
    - International Association of Police Chiefs, 1931-1934 (Box 25, Folder 356)
    - Joint Committee on the Improvement of Criminal Justice, 1932-1934 (Box 25, Folder 357)
    - Judicial Council of New Jersey, 1935-1936 (Box 25, Folder 358)
    - Karpman Study of the Criminally Insane, 1929-1930 (Box 25, Folder 359)
    - Laboratory of Social Hygiene - Bedford Hills, 1912-1913 (Box 25, Folder 360)
    - League of Nations Penal Administration, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 361)
    - Massachusetts Prison Association Parole Study, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 362)
    - "Measuring Crime vs. Estimating Crime" by Leonard Harrison, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 363)
    - Merriam, Charles, 1927-1933 (Box 25, Folder 364)
    - "Microscopy" by Albert Schneider, 1929-1930 (Box 25, Folder 365)
    - Minnesota Parole Study, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 366)
    - Minnesota Prisons, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 367)
    - National Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement, 1929-1935 (Box 25, Folder 368)
    - National Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement, 1929-1935 (Box 25, Folder 369)
    - National Commission on Law Observance and Enforcement - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 370)
    - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor, 1928-1935 (Box 26, Folder 371)
    - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor, 1928-1935 (Box 26, Folder 372)
    - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor, 1928-1935 (Box 26, Folder 373)
    - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor, 1928-1935 (Box 26, Folder 374)
    - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor - Clippings and Pamphlets (Box 26, Folder 375)
    - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor - Clippings and Pamphlets (Box 26, Folder 376)
    - National Committee on Public Education for Crime Control, 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 377)
    - National Crime Commission, 1930-1932 (Box 26, Folder 378)
    - National Police Council, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 379)
    - National Prison Emergency Committee, 1930-1931 (Box 26, Folder 380)
    - National Probation Association, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 381)
    - New York Prison Association, 1930-1934 (Box 27, Folder 382)
    - New York Prison Association, 1930-1934 (Box 27, Folder 383)
    - New York Prison Association - Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 384)
    - Nonpayment of Fines, 1927-1928 (Box 27, Folder 385)
    - Northwestern Criminal Law Administration Program, 1930 (Box 27, Folder 386)
    - Osborn Association (National Society of Penal Information), 1922-1935 (Box 27, Folder 387)
    - Osborn Association (National Society of Penal Information), 1922-1935 (Box 27, Folder 388)
    - Osborn Association (National Society of Penal Information), 1922-1935 (Box 27, Folder 389)
    - Osborn Association (National Society of Penal Information), 1922-1935 (Box 27, Folder 390)
    - Panzran, Carl #31614 United States Penitentiary Leavenworth - "My Ideas, My Complaints, My Suggestions", 1930 (Box 27, Folder 391)
    - Parole, 1928-1936 (Box 27, Folder 392)
    - Philadelphia Municipal Court, 1929-1930 (Box 27, Folder 393)
    - Police, 1914-1936 (Box 28, Folder 394)
    - Police, 1914-1936 (Box 28, Folder 395)
    - Police, 1914-1936 (Box 28, Folder 396)
    - Police Education (Box 28, Folder 397)
    - Police Social Service Fund, 1917-1918 (Box 28, Folder 398)
    - Police Training Schools, 1927-1936 (Box 28, Folder 399)
    - Police Training Schools, 1927-1936 (Box 28, Folder 400)
    - Police Training Schools, 1927-1936 (Box 28, Folder 401)
    - Police Training Schools, 1927-1936 (Box 28, Folder 402)
    - Police Training Schools, 1927-1936 (Box 28, Folder 403)
    - Police Training Schools - Colorado, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 404)
    - Police Training Schools - New York, 1929-1931 (Box 28, Folder 405)
    - Police Training Schools - New York, 1929-1931 (Box 28, Folder 406)
    - Police Training Schools - New York, 1932-1934 (Box 29, Folder 407)
    - Police Training Schools - New York - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 408)
    - Police Training Schools - Oregon (Box 29, Folder 409)
    - Police Training Schools - Rhode Island, 1929-1934 (Box 29, Folder 410)
    - Police Training Schools - Virginia, 1929-1932 (Box 29, Folder 411)
    - Police Training Schools - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 412)
    - Policewomen, 1928-1932 (Box 29, Folder 413)
    - Policewomen, 1928-1932 (Box 29, Folder 414)
    - "Policewomen's Manual" by Eleanor Hutzel, 1928-June 1932 (Box 29, Folder 415)
    - "Policewomen's Manual" by Eleanor Hutzel, 1928-June 1932 (Box 29, Folder 416)
    - "Policewomen's Manual" by Eleanor Hutzel, 1928-June 1932 (Box 29, Folder 417)
    - "Policewomen's Manual" by Eleanor Hutzel, July 1932-1935 (Box 30, Folder 418)
    - "Policewomen's Manual" by Eleanor Hutzel, July 1932-1935 (Box 30, Folder 419)
    - "Policewomen's Manual" - Distribution (Box 30, Folder 420)
    - "Policewomen's Manual" - Notes (Box 30, Folder 421)
    - "Policewomen's Manual" - Notes (Box 30, Folder 422)
    - Prison Architecture, 1930-1934 (Box 30, Folder 423)
    - Prison Diets, 1931-1932 (Box 30, Folder 424)
    - Prisoners Employment Service, 1931-1932 (Box 30, Folder 425)
    - Prison Libraries, 1929-1933 (Box 30, Folder 426)
    - "Prison Life in the Soviet Union" by Elias Tobenkin, 1932-1935 (Box 30, Folder 427)
    - Prisons, 1924-1932 (Box 30, Folder 428)
    - Prisons, 1924-1932 (Box 30, Folder 429)
    - Prisons, 1933-1936 (Box 31, Folder 430)
    - Probation, 1928-1935 (Box 31, Folder 431)
    - Probation, 1928-1935 (Box 31, Folder 432)
    - Probation - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 433)
    - Probation Forms - Erie County, New York, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 434)
    - Probation Schools, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 435)
    - Probation Schools - Curriculum (Box 31, Folder 436)
    - Psychiatry and Crime Prevention, 1930 (Box 31, Folder 437)
    - "Rural Criminal Justice" by Bruce Cobb, 1925-1934 (Box 31, Folder 438)
    - Sacco and Vanzetti, 1927 (Box 31, Folder 439)
    - Scandinavian Study, 1930 (Box 31, Folder 440)
    - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation, 1933-1934 (Box 31, Folder 441)
    - "Scientific Aspects of Crime" by Max Winsor, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 442)
    - Scientific Crime Detection Lab, 1928-1934 (Box 32, Folder 443)
    - Scientific Crime Detection Lab, 1928-1934 (Box 32, Folder 444)
    - Seabury Investigation, 1930-1932 (Box 32, Folder 445)
    - "Single Fingerprints", 1930-1934 (Box 32, Folder 446)
    - "Single Fingerprints", 1930-1934 (Box 32, Folder 447)
    - "Single Fingerprints", 1930-1934 (Box 32, Folder 448)
    - "Single Fingerprints", 1930-1934 (Box 32, Folder 449)
    - "Society's Offenders" by E. H. Sutherland, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 450)
    - State Police, 1934-1935 (Box 32, Folder 451)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts, 1929-1931 (Box 32, Folder 452)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts, 1929-1931 (Box 32, Folder 453)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts, 1932-1937 (Box 33, Folder 454)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts, 1932-1937 (Box 33, Folder 455)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts, 1932-1937 (Box 33, Folder 456)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts, 1932-1937 (Box 33, Folder 457)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts, 1932-1937 (Box 33, Folder 458)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts - Diary, 1932-April 1933 (Box 33, Folder 459)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts - Diary, 1932-April 1933 (Box 33, Folder 460)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts - Diary, 1932-April 1933 (Box 33, Folder 461)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts - Diary, 1932-April 1933 (Box 33, Folder 462)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts - Diary, 1932-April 1933 (Box 33, Folder 463)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts - Diary, May-December 1933 (Box 34, Folder 464)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts - Diary, May-December 1933 (Box 34, Folder 465)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts - Diary, May-December 1933 (Box 34, Folder 466)
    - State Prison Colony, Norfolk, Massachusetts - Howard Gill, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 467)
    - Stearns, Warren, 1929-1934 (Box 34, Folder 468)
    - "Therapeutic Value of Psychiatry as Applied in Our Penal Institutions" by Max Winsor (Box 34, Folder 469)
    - Thomas, W. I., 1928-1934 (Box 34, Folder 470)
    - Thomas, W. I., 1928-1934 (Box 34, Folder 471)
    - Thomas, W. I. - Reports (Box 34, Folder 472)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Abstracts (Box 35, Folder 473)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Methods (Box 35, Folder 474)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Biological Factors (Box 35, Folder 475)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Anthropological Factors (Box 35, Folder 476)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Physiological Factors (Box 35, Folder 477)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Psychological Factors (Box 35, Folder 478)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Sociological Factors (Box 35, Folder 479)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Economic Factors (Box 35, Folder 480)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Statistics (Box 35, Folder 481)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Prison and Reformatories (Box 35, Folder 482)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Probation (Box 35, Folder 483)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Parole (Box 35, Folder 484)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Juvenile Detention (Box 35, Folder 485)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Crime Prevention (Box 35, Folder 486)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Psychopathology (Box 35, Folder 487)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Recidivism (Box 35, Folder 488)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Criminal Organizations (Box 35, Folder 489)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Courts and Legal Procedures (Box 35, Folder 490)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Police (Box 35, Folder 491)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Narcotics (Box 35, Folder 492)
    - Thomas, W. L. - Crime and Psychopathology - Prostitution and Homosexuality (Box 35, Folder 493)
    - "Undermining Crime" by Leonard Harrison, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 494)
    - Uniform Crime Classification, 1932-1934 (Box 36, Folder 495)
    - Uniform Crime Classification, 1932-1934 (Box 36, Folder 496)
    - Uniform Crime Classification, 1932-1934 (Box 36, Folder 497)
    - United States Federation of Justice, 1927-1928 (Box 36, Folder 498)
    - University of California, 1929-1934 (Box 36, Folder 499)
    - University of Lwow, 1929-1930 (Box 36, Folder 500)
    - University of Southern California, 1929-1930 (Box 36, Folder 501)
    - Voluntary Defenders Committee, 1928-1930 (Box 36, Folder 502)
    - Welfare League Association, 1928-1932 (Box 36, Folder 503)
    - Welfare League Association, 1928-1932 (Box 36, Folder 504)
    - Women's Prison Association, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 505)
    - "Women's Reformatories in the United States", 1930-1931 (Box 37, Folder 506)
    - Women's Reformatories, 1930-1935 (Box 37, Folder 507)
    - Women's Reformatories, 1930-1935 (Box 37, Folder 508)
  - Projects - Miscellaneous, 3_5
    This subseries contains information not administrative but in which the Bureau had a special interest, such as the Institute for Family Relations, The Ohio Institute, and housing.
    - American Orthopsychiatric Association, 1932-1933 (Box 38, Folder 509)
    - American Sociological Society, 1930-1931 (Box 38, Folder 510)
    - Buffalo Municipal Research Bureau, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 511)
    - Case Work Forms, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 512)
    - Clippings (Box 38, Folder 513)
    - Clippings (Box 38, Folder 514)
    - Directories of Social Agencies, 1931-1932 (Box 38, Folder 515)
    - Emergency Exchange, 1932-1933 (Box 38, Folder 516)
    - George Junior Republic, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 517)
    - Housing, 1927-1934 (Box 38, Folder 518)
      Sunnyside Co-ops (New York City) and Radburn, New Jersey.
    - Institute of Family Relations, 1931-1932 (Box 38, Folder 519)
    - Institute of Human Relations, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 520)
    - Leprosy Eradication Fund, 1927-1929 (Box 38, Folder 521)
    - Mussolini City, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 522)
      Westchester County, New York.
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1928-1931 (Box 38, Folder 523)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1928-1931 (Box 38, Folder 524)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1932-1935 (Box 39, Folder 525)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1932-1935 (Box 39, Folder 526)
    - National Consumer's League, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 527)
    - National Health Council, 1928 (Box 39, Folder 528)
    - Ohio Institute, 1928-1933 (Box 39, Folder 529)
    - Ohio Institute, 1928-1933 (Box 39, Folder 530)
    - Ohio Institute, 1928-1933 (Box 39, Folder 531)
    - Ohio Institute - Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 532)
    - Open Road, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 533)
    - People's Foundation, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 534)
    - President's Emergency Committee for Unemployment, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 535)
    - Puerto Rico, 1928 (Box 39, Folder 536)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1928-1929 (Box 39, Folder 537)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1930-1933 (Box 40, Folder 538)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1930-1933 (Box 40, Folder 539)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1930-1933 (Box 40, Folder 540)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1930-1933 (Box 40, Folder 541)
    - Social Science Research Council - Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 542)
    - Social Sciences (Box 40, Folder 543)
    - Soldiers and Sailors Club, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 544)
    - Sunnyside Housing Project, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 545)
      Queens, New York.
    - Traffic - 5th Avenue and 42nd, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 546)
    - Traveller's Aid Society, 1925 (Box 40, Folder 547)
    - University Housing, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 548)
      Dormitory for SUNY Oswego.
    - Wakefield National Memorial Association, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 549)
- Leonard V. Harrison Files, 4
  Scholarly access to original archival material is permitted. User copies of microfilm are also available. The Leonard V. Harrison Files are reproduced in the microfilm publication of the Bureau of Social Hygiene project and research files, 1913-1940, reels 21-31 (Scholarly Resources Inc., 1980).
  Subseries 1 - Narcotics (2 boxes) Subseries 2 - European Police Systems (12 boxes) Subseries 3 - Boston-Harvard Survey (4 boxes) Subseries 4 - Criminology (6 boxes) Subseries 5 - Miscellaneous (2 boxes)
  This series consists of Leonard Harrison's own files, as distinct from the Bureau's files. There is much material in this series which relates to studies in Series 3 - Projects. In fact, much of this series is background research for those projects. Research in Series 3 will be more fruitful if this series is also consulted.
  - Leonard V. Harrison Files - Narcotics, 4_1
    - Case Notes (Box 1, Folder 550)
    - Case Notes (Box 1, Folder 551)